<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-08-08T19:41:45-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">joah.tech</title><author><name>Joah Reason</name><email>joahreason@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">My Resume</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/resume-markdown/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Resume" /><published>2023-08-08T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2023-08-08T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/posts/resume-markdown</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/posts/resume-markdown/"><![CDATA[<h1 id="about-me">About Me</h1>
<p>Hey! I’m <a href="##" title="J-OH-uh">Joah</a>. I am a software engineer with 3+ years of professional experience in the games industry. I have worked at multiple companies, on multiple titles for slot games, card games, and keno games! I love games, art, and programming. This passion has led me to a career that I love, and a fun hobby. In my personal time I have participated in several game jams, and <em>always</em> have some personal projects that I’m working on.</p>

<p><strong>Skills:</strong></p>
<ul>
  <li>Unity3D, Godot, Git, Octopus, Bamboo, Docker</li>
  <li>C#, Python, HTML, Javascript/Typescript, Java, and more</li>
  <li>Continuous Integration &amp; Delivery</li>
  <li>Learning and adapting to any new tool or framework</li>
  <li>Takes ownership over what is given, with the goal of maintaining and improving</li>
  <li>Accepts and gives opinions candidly, with the goal of reaching the best decision no matter the situation</li>
</ul>

<hr />

<h1 id="experience">Experience</h1>
<h4 id="draftkings---software-engineer"><a href="https://www.draftkings.com/">Draftkings</a> - <em>Software Engineer</em></h4>
<p><strong><em>July 2022 - Now</em></strong><br />
Currently I am on a small team of developers focused on supporting and improving the infrastructure used to create and deploy our iGaming casino games. Since starting I have taken responsibility of the process for deploying these games and shipped hundreds of updates to our catalog.</p>

<h4 id="grover-gaming---game-developer"><a href="https://grovergaming.com/">Grover Gaming</a> - <em>Game Developer</em></h4>
<p><strong><em>July 2020 - June 2022</em></strong><br />
I worked as the main developer of a small studio team, and worked on multiple slot and keno style games. The studio team consisted of 3 artists, 2 QA testers, and a producer. We remastered the company’s best selling game in Unity. My team and I maintained effectiveness while working remotely for 6 months during quarantine because of Covid-19.</p>

<hr />

<h1 id="education">Education</h1>
<h4 id="university-of-north-carolina-charlotte"><a href="https://www.charlotte.edu/">University of North Carolina Charlotte</a></h4>
<ul>
  <li>Charlotte, NC</li>
  <li>BS Computer Science</li>
  <li>August 2017 - May 2020</li>
  <li>Minor in mathematics. Concentration in Software, Systems, &amp; Networks.</li>
  <li>Participated in Game Development Club, placed second in Quarantine Game Jam.</li>
</ul>

<hr />

<h4 id="nash-community-college"><a href="https://nashcc.edu/">Nash Community College</a></h4>
<ul>
  <li>Rocky Mount, NC</li>
  <li>Associate in Science</li>
  <li>August 2015 - May 2017</li>
  <li>Took Intro to Programming classes, Physics, Calculus I - V, Technical Communication.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Joah Reason</name><email>joahreason@gmail.com</email></author><category term="resume" /><category term="professional" /><category term="work" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[About Me Hey! I’m Joah. I am a software engineer with 3+ years of professional experience in the games industry. I have worked at multiple companies, on multiple titles for slot games, card games, and keno games! I love games, art, and programming. This passion has led me to a career that I love, and a fun hobby. In my personal time I have participated in several game jams, and always have some personal projects that I’m working on. Skills: Unity3D, Godot, Git, Octopus, Bamboo, Docker C#, Python, HTML, Javascript/Typescript, Java, and more Continuous Integration &amp; Delivery Learning and adapting to any new tool or framework Takes ownership over what is given, with the goal of maintaining and improving Accepts and gives opinions candidly, with the goal of reaching the best decision no matter the situation Experience Draftkings - Software Engineer July 2022 - Now Currently I am on a small team of developers focused on supporting and improving the infrastructure used to create and deploy our iGaming casino games. Since starting I have taken responsibility of the process for deploying these games and shipped hundreds of updates to our catalog. Grover Gaming - Game Developer July 2020 - June 2022 I worked as the main developer of a small studio team, and worked on multiple slot and keno style games. The studio team consisted of 3 artists, 2 QA testers, and a producer. We remastered the company’s best selling game in Unity. My team and I maintained effectiveness while working remotely for 6 months during quarantine because of Covid-19. Education University of North Carolina Charlotte Charlotte, NC BS Computer Science August 2017 - May 2020 Minor in mathematics. Concentration in Software, Systems, &amp; Networks. Participated in Game Development Club, placed second in Quarantine Game Jam. Nash Community College Rocky Mount, NC Associate in Science August 2015 - May 2017 Took Intro to Programming classes, Physics, Calculus I - V, Technical Communication.]]></summary></entry></feed>